jackmedia.com.au 2016-06-30

# Jack Media | Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the JackMedia affiliate network website (the "Site"). Jack Media Pty Ltd (“JackMedia”, “We” or “Us”) is committed to protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected from our users (each a “User” or “You”). We provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to explain our information practices and the choices You can make about the way your information is used by Us. This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by JackMedia.

###  **Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy**

You must agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, including our use of cookies, in order to use the Site, to register an account ("Account") with the JackMedia affiliate network ("Affiliate Network"), or to log in to your Account as member of the Affiliate Network. Your acceptance of both this Privacy Policy and our use of cookies on the Site shall be deemed a blanket acceptance of such Privacy Policy and cookie usage for all future attempts to use the Site or to login and access your Account. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorised to register for an Account on the Affiliate Network and you must not continue using the Site.

###  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a clear and conspicuous notice on the Site explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site, use of your Account and/or acceptance of our email communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

###  **Email subscriptions**

We will not use your email address inappropriately. You may unsubscribe at any time!

  * ###  We will respect your request to opt-out of promotional messages immediately.

  * We respect the privacy of our Users and will aim to send only the most relevant messages.
  * Your data will be managed with your privacy in mind.
  * If your details have been added in error, please notify Us and We will remove them immediately.
  * Please be aware that We send third party communications and promotions. Your details are never sold or passed on to these third parties without your express consent in the form of an opt in box.

You may at any time choose to stop receiving emails containing general information regarding JackMedia by following the “unsubscribe” instructions at the end of each such email or by contacting us at support@jackmedia.com.au. Should you be contacted by our Third Party Agent through email, you can follow the instructions at the end of each such email to stop receiving such emails. There may be a short delay of up to several business days while your request is being verified, deployed and processed across our servers. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your Account, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you.

###  **Affiliate Network Accounts**

When You register for an Account on the Affiliate Network, We use a password-protected third party portal to store your personal information, and we may share your personal information with such third party ("Third Party Agent") as is necessary for the performance of your Account and the Affiliate Network.

###  **Personally identifiable information**

We may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register for an Account, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, or otherwise choose to provide personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This may include, but is not limited to: your name, business entity name. your title within the business, as well as your personal and/or business entity related e-mail address, mailing address, daytime and/or mobile telephone numbers, fax number, account information (or other information that we require in order to pay any amounts due to you under the Affiliate Network) and/or any other information that we request or you choose to provide.

Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personally identifiable information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to Us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that this may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities, creating or accessing an Account, or doing business with us if they do not provide the information that We need.

###  **Non-personally identifiable information**

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about Users whenever they interact with our Site and/or register for an Account on the Affiliate Network. Non-personally identifiable information may include the name and version of the browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, etc.), the type of computer or device you are using (e.g., PC, Mac, mobile phone, etc.), the operating system (e.g., Windows, Mac OS, Android), the domain name of your service provider (e.g., Telstra, Optus, etc.) and other technical information about Users' means of connection to our Site. We use the non-personally identifiable information that We collect, and share such information with our Third Party Agent, to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalise your experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyse Site usage.

###  **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance Users’ experiences. Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer. Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences, to help Us recognise You when You visit the Site again, and to keep You logged in to your Account when You use the Site.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies. You may choose to set your web browser to block cookies or to alert You when cookies are being sent. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you change computers, operating systems or browsers, or use multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser. If You block cookies from the Site, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. For example, you cannot register for or log in to an Account on the Affiliate Network without accepting the cookies that we use with the Site. For more specific information on the cookies we use, please see Exhibit A, below.

Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. We use cookies to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site.

###  **Web beacons**  
We may collect information using web beacons, which are commonly referred to in the industry as web bugs, pixel tags or clear GIFs. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on the Site, in your Account, or in the emails We send to You to deliver cookies, count visits and determine if an email has been opened and acted upon.

###  **End User information (business clients only)**

We do not collect personally identifiable information about your end users (“End Users”). However, we do use cookies to track anonymous traffic data about your end users. When end users who visit member affiliate sites click on the advertisements they have chosen to display through their Accounts on the Affiliate Network, we will utilise cookies and/or web beacons to track such end users’ activities at our merchant site(s). In certain circumstances, we may use cookie-less tracking methods to track such end users.

###  **Use of Information**

We collect and use Users’ personally identifiable information for the following purposes:

  * Personalising Users’ experiences

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  * Improving our Site

We continually strive to improve our Site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from Users.

  * Improving customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

  * Sending periodic emails

The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

  * Offering targeted products and services

When you complete a survey on the Site and respond affirmatively to questions about particular organisations/suppliers, You agree that JackMedia may use the information You provide to send You information about promotions, offers, products and services about those organisations/suppliers and may supply your contact information and survey responses to those organisations/suppliers that may use them to contact you by mail, phone or email for an indefinite period or until you opt out from the named organisation/supplier. Some of these organisations/suppliers may be based overseas.

We also use your personally identifiable information: (a) to send you information regarding your Account and the Affiliate Network; (b) to track your compliance with our terms, agreements and policies; and/or (c) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. You agree that we, or our Third Party Agent, may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your Account on the Affiliate Network.

###  **Information sharing and disclosure**

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, we will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to or with others. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative or program management services in connection with your Account. Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by us.

We may share personally identifiable information with third parties with your express consent. For example, if You request to receive information from a third party when You complete a survey, we may share your personally identifiable information with that third party.

We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of JackMedia. For example, we may disclose how frequently Users visit the Site on average or other demographic details about the membership database.

We reserve the right to share your personally identifiable information: (a) where required to do so by law; (b) to respond to a subpoena, search warrant, request by a court, or other legal process, whether or not a response is legally required; (c) where You are, or We believe You are, in violation of any terms, agreements, policies or laws; (d) in the case of a dispute; (e) where We determine, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or a third party, or necessary to protect Us from liability of any kind; (f) exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection or credit checks; and (g) in the event of any reorganisation, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock.

###  **International transfer of data**

We may transfer information that we collect about You (and your End Users, in the case of business clients), including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Laws governing data collection and use may differ from those in force in your jurisdiction. You consent to the disclosure of your information internationally and acknowledge that JackMedia will not be liable for the use of information by third parties and the data protection laws in your jurisdiction will not apply to information disclosed internationally.

###  **Confidentiality and security**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

We endeavour to safeguard and protect Users’ information. When Users submit personally identifiable information on the Site, their personally identifiable information is protected both online and offline.

Accounts are password-protected so that only You and JackMedia have access to this personal information. You may edit your registration data by using your password.

When our Account registration process requests Sensitive Information (such as bank account information and/or credit card information), and when we transmit such Sensitive Information, that Sensitive Information is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we protect all other user information online and offline. The Third Party Agent servers that we utilise to store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure physical environment. The Third Party Agent has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information stored on its servers.

Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data on or through our Site is at your own risk. However, access to your personally identifiable information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees, and Third Party Agents, that need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all User information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable laws, We shall notify You and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that We learn of an information security breach with respect to your personally identifiable information. Where possible, You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

You acknowledge that you provide your personally identifiable information to us with knowledgeable consent and at your own risk.

###  **Data retention**

Subject to any mandatory obligations to delete data or to mandatory record-keeping requirements, your information may be retained by Us and in our Third Party Agent portal, server logs, databases and records indefinitely.

###  **Third party websites and trademarks**

The Site may contain links to third-party websites ("Third Party Websites"), such as websites of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors and licensors. Please be aware that We do not control and are not responsible the content or links that appear on Third Party Websites or for the privacy practices they employ. In addition, these Third Party Websites may be constantly changing.

Browsing and interaction on any Third Party Website, including websites which have a link from our Site, is subject to that Third Party Website's own terms and policies. We encourage You to be aware when You leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Third Party Website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site.

JackMedia is not affiliated with, sponsored by or endorsed by any of the third-party products or retailers mentioned on the Site. Trademarks, service marks and logos (including, without limitation, the individual names of products and retailers) are the property of their respective owners.

###  **Minors**

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. We will never knowingly collect any personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If We obtain actual knowledge that We have collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

###  **Employees (business clients only)**

Acceptance of this Privacy Policy by a business client shall extend to its employees, if any. You agree that any of your employees that access your Account, or visit the Site under the scope of their employment with You, agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

###  **Advertising**  
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognise your computer each time they send You an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about You or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###  **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the Dynamic Advertising Reporting & Targeting (DART) cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other websites on the Internet. DART uses non-personally identifiable information and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

###  **Deleting and updating your information**

If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that We have collected from you, simply email us at [support@jackmedia.com.au](mailto:support@jackmedia.com.au). We will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, We will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

You can also update certain information in your Account by logging in on this Site and following the prompts in the “My Account” section.

###  **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or your dealings with this Site, or if you wish to make a complaint about how We handle personal information, please contact us at:

We will endeavour to respond to your query within five business days.

_This document was last updated on 13 March 2014._
